

## CONTACT



Phone: 00 216 21652094



Mail:

belhssanklouz@gmail.com



Web:

www.belhssanklouz.github.io

#### SKILLS

Redux

Wordpress NodeJS

Javascript ExpressJS

¡Query Mongodb/Mongoose

Photoshop

ReactJS MySQL

Git/Github Illustrator

Styled component CI/CD

# **LANGUAGES**

French Intermediate
English Professional
Arabic Mother Tongue

#### SOCIAL

**Linkedin** Linkedin.com/in/belhssanklouz

Github
Github.com/belhssanklouz

# Belhssan Klouz

Frontend Developer

Graduated in the field of Information and Communication Technology Management and now working as Web Developer at CLS. Interested in the field of Frontend Development in general and in particular in areas related to Design and Implementation of UI. Also interested in privacy awareness and good practices. I like to do research to gain more knowledge and improve myself.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

O Consulting at Logiciels and Systemes | Tunisia

Oct 2020 - Current

#### WEB DEVELOPER

- Design and implementation of sales control web application.
- Participate in the development of RESTAPI.
- Design and implementation of websites on Wordpress and deployment on  $\ensuremath{\mathsf{OVH}}$

Skills: NodeJS, ExpressJS, MongoDB, JWT, ReactJS, Redux, Wordpress, jQuery

Mind Engineering | Bardo, Tunisia

Feb 2020 - Jul 2020

#### INTERN WEB DEVELOPER

- Developed features of a school managament application.
- Design and implementation of a landing page.
- Designed visual identity for the application.

Skills: PHP, Wordpress, HTML, CSS, Javascript, Photoshop, Illustrator

#### **EDUCATION**

OF ICT MANAGEMENT
Sept 2017 - Jul 2020

Higher Institute of Technological Studies in Communications of Tunis (iset'com) | Tunisia

#### **PROJECTS**

#### E-Commerce App

04/2022 - 06/2022

#### **FULL STACK MERN**

- Development of backend server and RESTAPI.
- Designed noSQL database architecture.
- Integrated authentication token JWT.
- Integrated Stripe payment module.
- Design and Implementation of front online store.
- Design and Implementation of dashboard to control the online store.

Skills: NodeJS, ExpressJS, MongoDB, JWT, ReactJS, Redux, Styled Component

#### 

03/2022 - 04/2022

### REACTIS AND FIREBASE

- Developed different Linkedin features in frontend side.
- Integrated Firebase Firestore as noSQL database.

Skills: ReactJS, Redux, Firestore, Firebase Auth, Styled Component